[{"answer": "Oh, hi.  Youre new in this building too, arent you?  My name is Shirley", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 15, "question": "", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Hi, Shirley.  Nice to meet you.  My name is Frank, and this is Bill.  Hes new too", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 16, "question": "Oh, hi.  Youre new in this building too, arent you?  My name is Shirley", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": "So, Frank, what do you do", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Hi, Shirley.  Nice to meet you.  My name is Frank, and this is Bill.  Hes new too", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": "I work over at the Athens Steel Company.  Im a production worker there", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 18, "question": "So, Frank, what do you do", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " What kind of work do you do for that position", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 19, "question": "I work over at the Athens Steel Company.  Im a production worker there", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Well, its actually pretty monotonous.  We build steel parts for engines there", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 20, "question": " What kind of work do you do for that position", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Do you have regular hours", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 24, "question": " Well, its actually pretty monotonous.  We build steel parts for engines there", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " No, we work in shifts.  Right now, I have the graveyard shift, so I work fro", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 25, "question": " Do you have regular hours", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " That must be hard", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 32, "question": " No, we work in shifts.  Right now, I have the graveyard shift, so I work fro", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " Its not so bad.  You get used to it.  Even though we work in shifts, its a full", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 33, "question": " That must be hard", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " I work full-time as a graphic designer", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 37, "question": " Its not so bad.  You get used to it.  Even though we work in shifts, its a full", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " Do you like it", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 38, "question": " I work full-time as a graphic designer", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " Oh, yeah.  I get to be very creative and design websites, print materials, an", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 39, "question": " Do you like it", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": "Havent I seen you walking around with your dog and daughter in the middle o", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 43, "question": " Oh, yeah.  I get to be very creative and design websites, print materials, an", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Im actually really lucky.  My position is a full-time salaried position, but I ge", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 47, "question": "Havent I seen you walking around with your dog and daughter in the middle o", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " What exactly does that mean", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 51, "question": " Im actually really lucky.  My position is a full-time salaried position, but I ge", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " It basically means that I can work flexible hours.  I have to work 40 hours ", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 52, "question": " What exactly does that mean", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " That sounds really great", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 56, "question": " It basically means that I can work flexible hours.  I have to work 40 hours ", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " It is.  Sometimes I work during the day, sometimes I go into the office in th", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 57, "question": " That sounds really great", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " Ive heard a lot of companies are starting to do that now.  Thats a great benefit fo", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 61, "question": " It is.  Sometimes I work during the day, sometimes I go into the office in th", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " It definitely is.  So, what do you do, Bill", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Ive heard a lot of companies are starting to do that now.  Thats a great benefit fo", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": "Im a computer technician", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 66, "question": " It definitely is.  So, what do you do, Bill", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " What exactly do you do for that", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 67, "question": "Im a computer technician", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " Basically, I repair computers for people when they have trouble with them", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 68, "question": " What exactly do you do for that", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": "What company do you work for", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 69, "question": " Basically, I repair computers for people when they have trouble with them", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": "None.  I work part-time as an independent contractor", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 70, "question": "What company do you work for", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " So, youre self-employed", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 71, "question": "None.  I work part-time as an independent contractor", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " Yep", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 75, "question": " So, youre self-employed", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " Wow.  That must be nice", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 76, "question": " Yep", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " It is.  I have a lot of flexibility in terms of my working hours and the work that ", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 77, "question": " Wow.  That must be nice", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": "How many hours a week do you usually work", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 81, "question": " It is.  I have a lot of flexibility in terms of my working hours and the work that ", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " It depends on how much work I have each week.  Usually around 20 hours a week", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 82, "question": "How many hours a week do you usually work", "qSentId": 81},{"answer": " You must have a lot of free time", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 83, "question": " It depends on how much work I have each week.  Usually around 20 hours a week", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " I do.  My stress levels have gone down a lot since I quit my full-time job and wen", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 84, "question": " You must have a lot of free time", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " You know, we have a computer at home thats been giving me some trouble", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 88, "question": " I do.  My stress levels have gone down a lot since I quit my full-time job and wen", "qSentId": 87},{"answer": " Sure.  Just give me a call, and I can come take a look", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 92, "question": " You know, we have a computer at home thats been giving me some trouble", "qSentId": 91},{"answer": " Well, Ive got to go pick up my daughter.  It was nice to meet you two", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 93, "question": " Sure.  Just give me a call, and I can come take a look", "qSentId": 92},{"answer": " Yeah, you too.  See you around", "docId": "01-01", "aSentId": 94, "question": " Well, Ive got to go pick up my daughter.  It was nice to meet you two", "qSentId": 93}]
